Guide to the Capitol Hill Restoration Society records, 1904-2012 MS2009
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Presidents' papers, 1955-1998; MS2009 Series 11; 13.5 Linear feet
  - Paul Hays: Eastern Market -- Community Steering Committee, Studies, Recommendations, 1982 (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Paul Hays: Eastern Market -- Market V Gallery, 1982 (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Paul Hays: Fund Raising, undated (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Paul Hays: Historic District, undated (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Paul Hays: House Tour, 1982 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Paul Hays: Legal -- Bylaws, 1983 April (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Paul Hays: Legal -- Certificate of Registration for Solicitation, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Paul Hays: Legal -- Voter Education Program, 1982 (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - Paul Hays: Membership -- Committee Members, correspondence, undated (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Paul Hays: Membership -- Correspondence to members, undated (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Paul Hays: Membership -- Data processing proposal, 1981 August 08 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Paul Hays: Membership -- Invitations to Join, undated (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Paul Hays: Membership -- List of Members, 1980-1981 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Paul Hays: Membership - List of Members, 1981 November 25 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Paul Hays: Membership -- Mailing Labels, undated (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Paul Hays: Membership -- Members not renewed, to call, 1980-1981 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Paul Hays: Membership -- Minutes of Meetings, 1981-1982 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Paul Hays: Membership -- Proposals, undated (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Paul Hays: Membership -- Renewal Letters, undated (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Paul Hays: Metropolitan Area Preservation, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Paul Hays: Police Station Study -- list of congressmen and senators living on Capitol Hill, undated (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Paul Hays: Program -- Candidates' Forum (Voter Education), 1982 Septemer 08 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Paul Hays: Public Safety Committee, undated (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Paul Hays: Safeway -- Fourteenth St. & Kentucky Ave., undated (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Paul Hays: Supreme Court Parking Lot, Third & A Streets, NE, undated (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Paul Hays: Taxes, undated (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Paul Hays: Traffic Task Force - Barney Circle, undated (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Paul Hays: Traffic Task Force -- Capitol Hill traffic problems, undated (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Paul Hays: Traffic Task Force -- Constitution Avenue, undated (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Paul Hays: Traffic Task Force -- Eleventh & Independence, undated (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Paul Hays: Traffic Task Force -- Map, Capitol Hill Traffic Map, undated (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Paul Hays: Traffic Task Force -- Meetings, Agenda and Minutes, undated (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Paul Hays: Treasurer -- Reports, undated (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Paul Hays: Video Arcade, 14th & E Streets, SE, undated (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Paul Hays: Yost House -- Certificate of Insurance, Wayward Books, undated (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - Paul Hays: Yost House -- Committee Goals, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - Paul Hays: Yost House -- Dedication Ceremony, 1980 October 19 (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - Paul Hays: Zoning -- C & P Building, 629 Constitution Avenue, undated (Box 64, Folder 30)
  - Paul Hays: Zoning -- Capitol Hill Hospital Parking, undated (Box 64, Folder 31)
  - Paul Hays: Zoning -- 218 E Street, SE, undated (Box 64, Folder 32)
  - Paul Hays: Zoning -- 637 East Capitol, garage height, undated (Box 64, Folder 33)
  - Paul Hays: Zoning -- Foreign Missions Act, undated (Box 64, Folder 34)
  - Paul Hays: Zoning -- Mt. Jezreel Baptist Church, Fifth & E Streets, SE, undated (Box 64, Folder 35)
  - Paul Hays: Zoning -- Supreme Court Historic Society, 111 Second Street, NE, undated (Box 64, Folder 36)
  - Paul Hays: Zoning -- 417-423 Third Street, NE, parking, undated (Box 64, Folder 37)
  - Paul Hays: Zoning -- Watterson House, 224 Second Street, SE, undated (Box 64, Folder 38)
  - Larry Monaco: Barney Circle Advisory Meeting, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Larry Monaco: Barney Circle Correspondence, undated (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Larry Monaco: Barney Circle Design Study Technical Coordinating Committee, undated (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Larry Monaco: Barney Circle Freeway Study contacts lists, 1985 July 03 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Larry Monaco: Barney Circle Maps, undated (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Larry Monaco: Barney Circle Newspaper Articles, Flyers, undated (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Larry Monaco: Barney Circle Parkway Evaluation, undated (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Larry Monaco: Barney Circle Photographs of Site, undated (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Larry Monaco: Barney Circle Testimony, Pat Schauer, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Larry Monaco: Bottle Deposit Bill, 1985-1986 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Larry Monaco: Business Residential Parking, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Larry Monaco: Children's Island (1), undated (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Larry Monaco: Children's Island (2), undated (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Larry Monaco: Civil Infractions Program, undated (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Larry Monaco: Conservation Easement Act of, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Larry Monaco: Corporate Report, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Larry Monaco: Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Larry Monaco: Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Larry Monaco: Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Larry Monaco: D.C. Alcoholic Beverage Control Act Reform Amendment press release, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Larry Monaco: D.C. Alcoholic Beverage Control Act Reform Amendment testimoney, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Larry Monaco: D.C. Boards & Commissions-Appointments, 1985 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Larry Monaco: D.C. Preservation Alliance, 1985-1986 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Larry Monaco: DC. Preservation League Newsletter, 1985-1986 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Larry Monaco: D.C. Prison, undated (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Larry Monaco: D.C. Stadium Transfer, undated (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Larry Monaco: Dupont Circle Citizens Newsletter, 1986-1987 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Larry Monaco: Eastern Market, 1985-1986 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Larry Monaco: Georgetown Citizens' Association Newsletter, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Larry Monaco: Heliport Study, Airport Noise, 1983-1984 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Larry Monaco: Historic District Committee, 1983-1987 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Larry Monaco: Kingman Island, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Larry Monaco: Lovejoy and Maury Schools, Alternate Use Study, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Larry Monaco: Marine Parking, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Larry Monaco: Membership, 1983 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Larry Monaco: Museum of African Art 316-330 A St. NE sale, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Larry Monaco: Museum of African Art (2), undated (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Larry Monaco: National Capital Planning Commission (1), undated (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Larry Monaco: National Capital Planning Commission (2), undated (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Larry Monaco: National Woman's Party, 1983 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Larry Monaco: Off Street Parking Requirements in an Historic District, undated (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Larry Monaco: Office Manager Contract, undated (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Larry Monaco: Parks-Anacostia River, undated (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Larry Monaco: Preservation Action Newsletter, undated (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Larry Monaco: Public Space, undated (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Larry Monaco: PUD Regulations, Zoning Commission, undated (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Larry Monaco: Safeway, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Larry Monaco: Sasha Bruce House, undated (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Larry Monaco: Sidewalk Repair and Replacement, undated (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Larry Monaco: Stanton Park Neighborhood Association, 1986-1987 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Larry Monaco: Tax Returns, 1983-1985 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Larry Monaco: Traffic Congestion, Pennsylvania Avenue, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Larry Monaco: Traffic General Traffic Management, undated (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Larry Monaco: Traffic Task Force, undated (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Larry Monaco: Union Station Area Development, undated (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Larry Monaco: Ward Plans, GW University, undated (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Larry Monaco: Yost House, undated (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Larry Monaco: Zoning--D.C. Property to be subject to zoning regulation, undated (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Larry Monaco: Zoning- McLachlen National Bank, undated (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Trudy Peterson: Board Meeting, 1987 June 1 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Trudy Peterson: Board Meeting, 1987 June 29 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Trudy Peterson: Board Meeting, 1987 August 24 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Trudy Peterson: Board Meeting, 1987 September 28 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Trudy Peterson: Board Meeting, 1987 November 30 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Trudy Peterson: Board Meeting, 1987 December 28 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Trudy Peterson: Board Meeting, 1988 January 25 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Trudy Peterson: Board Meeting, 1988 February 06 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Trudy Peterson: Board Meeting, 1988 February 28 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Trudy Peterson: Board Meeting, 1988 March 28 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Trudy Peterson: Board Meeting, 1987 April 25 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Trudy Peterson: Budget -- Proposed, 1987-1988 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Trudy Peterson: City Planning, Comprehensive Plan, Draft Action Plan, Potomac Avenue Metro Station, Ward 6, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Trudy Peterson: City Planning -- Condemnation Proceedings Act. Hearing Notices and correspondence, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - Trudy Peterson: City Planning- Union Station Area Proposal for new federal office building, 1988 January - February (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - Trudy Peterson: Community Relations-Eastern Market Report, Neighborhood Commission, 1987 June 30 (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Trudy Peterson: Community Relations Champs Directory, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - Trudy Peterson: Community Relations Legislation in Police Districts, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - Trudy Peterson: Community Relation, Neighborhood Watch Newsletter, 1987 August 08 (Box 68, Folder 25)
  - Trudy Peterson: Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 68, Folder 26)
  - Trudy Peterson: Directory, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 27)
  - Trudy Peterson: Environment-Barney Circle, correspondence, notes, testimony, 1987-1988 (Box 68, Folder 28)
  - Trudy Peterson: Environment-Bottle Bill, correspondence, flyer, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Trudy Peterson: Environment-Chairman's (Pat Schauer's) notes to President, 1987-1988 (Box 68, Folder 30)
  - Trudy Peterson: Environment-City Post Office Traffic Management Program, correspondence, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 31)
  - Trudy Peterson: Environment-Committee Members, 1986-1987 (Box 68, Folder 32)
  - Trudy Peterson: Environment-D.C. Jail, new prison site, correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 68, Folder 33)
  - Trudy Peterson: Environment Fourth and Sixth Sts. 2-way proposal, correspondence, testimony, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 34)
  - Trudy Peterson: Environment - National Airport, correspondence, articles, testimony, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 35)
  - Trudy Peterson: Environment -- National Airport, report by Citizens for the Abatement of Aircraft Noise, Inc., 1987 November 12 (Box 68, Folder 36)
  - Trudy Peterson: Environment -- Old City Post Office, correspondence, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 37)
  - Trudy Peterson: Environment -- Traffic Task force, meetings, correspondence, articles, undated (Box 68, Folder 38)
  - Trudy Peterson: Environment -- Trash and Snow Removal, correspondence, brochures, undated (Box 68, Folder 39)
  - Trudy Peterson: Financial Statement, 1987 August 31 (Box 68, Folder 40)
  - Trudy Peterson: Historic District -- Committee Members, 1986 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Trudy Peterson: Historic District -- Marketable Row, Hill Rag article re: Old Safeway Building, 1987 June 05 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Trudy Peterson: Historic District -- Monitor's Schedule, 1987-1988 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Trudy Peterson: Historic District- Preservation Law Update, 1987 November 12 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Trudy Peterson: House Tour, forms, letters and notices to homeowners, 1988 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Trudy Peterson: House Tour, Committee Members, 1988 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Trudy Peterson: House Tour -- Subscription Summary, 1988 May (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Trudy Peterson: House Tours -- thank you letters, undated (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Trudy Peterson: Legal and Litigation. Board Procedures Handbook, draft, undated (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Trudy Peterson: Membership, Alphabetical List, 1988 January 31 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Trudy Peterson: Membership -- Committee Members, 1986-1987 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Trudy Peterson: Membership form letter re: expiration, 1987 September (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Trudy Peterson: Membership Meetings, 1988 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Trudy Peterson: Membership Survey, 1976-1978 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Trudy Peterson: Membership survey, undated (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Trudy Peterson: Office management, undated (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Trudy Peterson: Publicity, letter to James Dean, 1987 September 13 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - Trudy Peterson: Yost House -- Deed, 1979 July 16 (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - Trudy Peterson: Yost House- Electrical Inspection Report, 1987 October 05 (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - Trudy Peterson: Yost House -- Goals, 1983 February (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - Trudy Peterson: Yost House -- Grant Application, 1978 July 19 (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - Trudy Peterson: Yost House -- Grant Contract, 1979 June (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - Trudy Peterson: Yost House -- Historic Preservation Covenant, 1979 August 20 (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Trudy Peterson: Yost House, memo of Understanding with Unitarian Universalist Congregation, undated (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - Trudy Peterson: Yost House -- Co-Chairmen, notes correspondence, undated (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Trudy Peterson: Yost House - Planning Report, 1987 November (Box 69, Folder 26)
  - Trudy Peterson: Yost House -- Request for proposal (for use and restoration report), 1988 March (Box 69, Folder 27)
  - Trudy Peterson: Yost House -- Statement of Accounts, 1987 May 31 (Box 69, Folder 28)
  - Trudy Peterson: Zoning -- 224 East Capitol Street, American Cancer Society, 1987 June 25 (Box 69, Folder 29)
  - Trudy Peterson: Zoning -- Chairman and Committee Members, Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Trudy Peterson: Zoning -- BZA Cases, 1987 September (Box 69, Folder 31)
  - Trudy Peterson: Zoning -- BZA Cases, 1987 October (Box 69, Folder 32)
  - Trudy Peterson: Zoning -- BZA Cases, 1987 November (Box 69, Folder 33)
  - Trudy Peterson: Zoning -- BZA Cases, 1988 January (Box 69, Folder 34)
  - Trudy Peterson: Zoning -- BZA Hearing (420 Tenth Street, SE), 1987 March (Box 69, Folder 35)
  - Trudy Peterson: Zoning - BZA Hearing, (730 -- 730A 15th Street, SE), 1986 December 03 (Box 69, Folder 36)
  - Trudy Peterson: Zoning -- BZA Hearing, Order (Denied) 303 Twelfth Street, SE REAR, 1987 March 31 (Box 69, Folder 37)
  - Trudy Peterson: Zoning -- BZA Hearing, Case 87-1, (re rooming houses), 1988 February 04 (Box 69, Folder 38)
  - Trudy Peterson: Zoning -- BZA Hearing, 214 South Carolina, 1988 (Box 69, Folder 39)
  - Trudy Peterson: Zoning -- Committee Members, 1983-1984 (Box 69, Folder 40)
  - Trudy Peterson: Zoning -- D.C. Government Publications, brochures, pamphlets, undated (Box 69, Folder 41)
  - Trudy Peterson: Zoning -- Newspaper Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 69, Folder 42)
  - Trudy Peterson: Zoning -- Proposed Addition to Seventh Street Safeway, notice of Meeting, 1988 April (Box 69, Folder 43)
  - Pat Schauer: Capitol Hill Hospital, correspondence, 1990 (Box 69, Folder 44)
  - Pat Schauer: Citizen's Guide to Ward Planning (Ward 6) Urban Planning Dept., GWU, 1986 (Box 69, Folder 45)
  - Pat Schauer: Committee on Noise Abatement at National and Dulles Airports, undated (Box 69, Folder 46)
  - Pat Schauer: Community Relations, 1988-1989 (Box 69, Folder 47)
  - Pat Schauer: Correspondence, Misc., 1988 (Box 69, Folder 48)
  - Pat Schauer: CSX Project -- Station Place, Architectural Plans, undated (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Pat Schauer: CSX Project -- Station Place, Capitol Hill Traffic Task Force, undated (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Pat Schauer: CSX Project -- Station Place, correspondence, incoming, 1989-1990 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Pat Schauer: CSX Project -- Station Place, correspondence, outgoing, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Pat Schauer: CSX Project -- Station Place, correspondence, Stanton Park Neighborhood Association, 1989-1990 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Pat Schauer: CSX Project -- Station Place, correspondence, third party and carbons, undated (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Pat Schauer: CSX Project -- Station Place, minutes of meetings, undated (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Pat Schauer: CSX Project -- Station Place, newspaper clippings, undated (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Pat Schauer: CSX Project -- Station Place, Supplemental Filing Application, 1990 July 10 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Pat Schauer: CSX Project -- Station Place, Transportation Management Plan, 1990 March 01 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Pat Schauer: D.C. Stadium, correspondence, undated (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Pat Schauer: D.C. Stadium, Feasibility Study for Expansion, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Pat Schauer: D.C. Stadium Newspaper Clippings, articles, undated (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Pat Schauer: D.C. Stadium, Parking Restrictions in adjoining neighborhood, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Pat Schauer: D.C. Stadium transfer of federal park land, hearings, issue sheets, U.S. Senate Act, undated (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Pat Schauer: Ellen Wilson, correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Pat Schauer: Ellen Wilson, draft, feasibility study, undated (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Pat Schauer: Ellen Wilson, Historic Review Board, CHRS testimony and Historic Preservation Office Staff Report, 1988 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Pat Schauer: Ellen Wilson, Newspaper Clippings and Articles, undated (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - Pat Schauer: Heliport/Netport, Second and K Street, NE, 1988-1989 (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - Pat Schauer: Judiciary Office Building, correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - Pat Schauer: Judiciary Office Building Act, draft report, undated (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - Pat Schauer: Judiciary Office Building, newspaper articles, 1987-1988 (Box 70, Folder 23)
  - Pat Schauer: Judiciary Office Building, Proposed Building, notes, undated (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Pat Schauer: Judiciary Office Building, Request for Proposal and Supplement, 1986 December (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Pat Schauer: Judiciary Office Building, U.S. Senate -1934, Bill, Hearing, Amendment to Reports, Congressional Record, 1986-1987 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Pat Schauer: Judiciary Office Building, U.S. Senate --1934, Testimony, undated (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Pat Schauer: Marine Parking issues, 700 block of Ninth Street, SE, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Pat Schauer: Old City Post Office, correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Pat Schauer: Old City Post Office, NCPC, meeting agenda, reports, etc., 1987-1988 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Pat Schauer: Old City Post Office, newspaper clippings, articles, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Pat Schauer: Old City Post Office, Renovation and Redevelopment Proposal, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Pat Schauer: Old City Post Office, Testimony, 1987-1988 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Pat Schauer: Police Districts, Reorganization, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Pat Schauer: Providence Park, 1989-1990 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Pat Schauer: Saint Elizabeth's Hospital -- History, undated (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Pat Schauer: Sasha Bruce House, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Pat Schauer: Senate Stables, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Pat Schauer: Union Station Area Traffic Studies, 1987-1988 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Pat Schauer: Union Station Area Traffic Impact Study, Final report, 1988 July (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Pat Schauer: Union Station Area Traffic Study --background issues, 1986-1988 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Pat Schauer: Union Station Merchandizing Plan, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Pat Schauer: Union Station, newspaper clippings, articles, undated (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Pat Schauer: Union Station/North Capitol Street Small Area Study, preliminary report (Zoning #89-3), undated (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Pat Schauer: Union Station/North Capitol Street Transportation Study (Bartin-Aschman Association), notes and correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Pat Schauer: Union Station Redevelopment Activities, undated (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Pat Schauer: Union Station Redevelopment, correspondence, undated (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Pat Schauer: Union Station Redevelopment, testimony before NCPC, 1987 May (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Pat Schauer: Union Station Redevelopment, Traffic Management Task Force, committee notes, undated (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Pat Schauer: Ward Six Plan, Architect of the Capitol, undated (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Pat Schauer: Ward Six Plan, Capitol Hill SE, undated (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Pat Schauer: Ward Six Plan, correspondence, committees, undated (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Pat Schauer: Ward Six Plan, Eighth Street Corridor, undated (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Pat Schauer: Ward Six Plan, Kingman Park, undated (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Pat Schauer: Ward Six Plan, Lincoln Park, undated (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Pat Schauer: Ward Six Plan, Lincoln Park East, undated (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Pat Schauer: Ward Six Plan, Massachusetts Avenue Corridor, undated (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Pat Schauer: Ward Six Plan, Near Northeast, undated (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Pat Schauer: Ward Six Plan, Pennsylvania Avenue Commercial Corridor, undated (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Pat Schauer: Ward Six Plan, Potomac SE, undated (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Pat Schauer: Ward Six Plan, Stanton Park, undated (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Pat Schauer: Woodward Building, Committee of 100 v. D.C. Government, undated (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Larry Pearl: Barney Circle, undated (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Larry Pearl: Capitol Hill Arts Workshop, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Larry Pearl: Congressional Cemetery, Barney Circle, undated (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Larry Pearl: Correspondence, miscellaneous, 1991-1992 (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Larry Pearl: Eastern Market, articles and newspaper clippings, undated (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - Larry Pearl: Eastern Market, "It's About Time" Campaign, undated (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - Larry Pearl: Eastern Market, Landmark Status Proposed for Interior, undated (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - Larry Pearl: Eastern Market, Preservation and Development Corporation, undated (Box 72, Folder 27)
  - Larry Pearl: Eastern Market Renovation, letters, testimony, etc., undated (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Larry Pearl: Eastern Market, "Save the Market" Campaign, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Larry Pearl: Ellen Wilson Study, 1991 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Larry Pearl: Financial Statements, 1990-1991 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Larry Pearl: Judiciary Office Building, parking issues, undated (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Larry Pearl: L'Enfant -- McMillan Plans, NPS, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Larry Pearl: Peabody School, undated (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Larry Pearl: Public Safety (D.C. Downsizing), undated (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Larry Pearl: Safeway, 14th and Kentucky Ave., landscaping, undated (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Larry Pearl: S.E. Federal Center, Eastern Portion, Draft Environmental Impact Statement, 1992 March (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Larry Pearl: S.E. Federal Center, Eastern Portion, Final Environmental Impact Statement, 1992 September (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Larry Pearl: Station Place, undated (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Larry Pearl: Street Trees, 1989-1991 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Larry Pearl: Trant's Liquors, 1991 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Larry Pearl: Union Station, undated (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Larry Pearl: Union Station/North Capitol Street, Zoning Commission Case 89-3, undated (Box 74, Folder 4)